{
  "age": 55,
  "background": "Law Enforcement, Fire Suppression, Prevention, Public  Safety, Emergency Medical Technician. Community service and Education.",
  "directory": "content/us-house/district-7",
  "district": 7,
  "dob": "3/24/1963",
  "education": "Criminal Justice, law enforcement, Fire Service, Emergency medical, public health and Safety",
  "filename": "anthony-sr-carter.md",
  "full-name": "Anthony Sr. Carter",
  "jurisdiction": "Baltimore City",
  "last-name": "Carter",
  "party": "Democrat",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "How do you assess the Trump administration so far?",
      "answer": "Trump Administration is suffering from a lack of experience with a high turnover , personal issues , tweeting  and Russian  problems.  Trump and his administration is  morally and ethically incapable of leading this country. We need a president and administration that understands, no man is greater  than the  office of  presidency This administration is reactive not proactive, like giving teachers guns . if teachers wanted guns they would have become police officers or building a wall. We should building a relationship with Mexico,  economically and securities. We tried being isolationistt as result World War II.  The president does not have a understanding of world history or anyone in his cabinet. Being  President of the United States is great honor with lots of responsibilities,   an example for our children and its citizens and the world. Being a Ceo or business owner is very different from being president.. Ceo/Businees owner is about  profit , loss and sales . Being President,  the Constitution and  the rule of law , leadership,  domestic and foreign affairs, President Trump and his administration has failed on all levels. I do not wish for the president and his administration failure because it will be a failure for our would country,  I love.",
      "shortname": "Trump record"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you support or oppose the federal tax cuts passed in 2017? What effect do you believe they will have on the economy?",
      "answer": "I oppose the federal tax cuts because it wil increase the federal deficit by 4 trillion or more  . It's irresponsible and affects our children's future",
      "shortname": "2017 Tax cuts"
    },
    {
      "question": "Is the level of national debt a concern? What, if anything, should be done to reduce it or constrain its increase?",
      "answer": "The level of nation debt is very concerning. like your personal budget before spending you should know where it's coming from.  Money being spent by both parties or a concern and should be kept in check. Congressman Elijah Cummings he wants to spend more money on the opioid crisis. What about the pharmaceutical companies Health Providers, Hospitals and doctors, paying for this crises . The politicians that accept big money from the pharmaceutical industry for that campaigns.",
      "shortname": "National debt"
    },
    {
      "question": "Is the level of economic inequality in the United States a problem, and if so, what should the federal government do to address it?",
      "answer": "the levelling of economic inequality in the United States . Bring down the cost of education,  help to develop small businesses ,  entrepreneurs ships , trades skills  and more small business loans",
      "shortname": "Income inequality"
    },
    {
      "question": "Should federal gun laws be changed, and if so, how?",
      "answer": "restrict the purchasing of assault  rifles with age limits and background checks. We take a test for a driver's license maybe a test to own a firearm, safety,  ethical or competency.",
      "shortname": "Gun laws"
    },
    {
      "question": "What should Congress do with respect to the Affordable Care Act? Should it be strengthened, and if so, how? Should it be scrapped? If so, what if anything should replace it?",
      "answer": "Congress should strengthen the Affordable Care Act because there is no replacement.Why throw out the baby with the bathwater.  keep what works and replace what does not work,  common sense",
      "shortname": "ACA"
    },
    {
      "question": "What role should the federal government play in helping cities like Baltimore?",
      "answer": "the federal government can help by providing affordable equal education, Business and Community Development.",
      "shortname": "Urban policy"
    },
    {
      "question": "What can Congress do to address the opioid epidemic?",
      "answer": "Congress is to accept responsibility and lack of oversight of the FDA approval of pharmaceutical drugs causing this epidemic.. The taxpayers should not bear the cost like the bank crisis. The  congress, pharmaceutical companies, hospitals and doctors are responsible for this crisis.",
      "shortname": "Opioids"
    },
    {
      "question": "What changes if any should Congress make to our immigration and deportation laws and policies?",
      "answer": "children born in this country should have a pathway to become citizens. having a relationship with Mexicoas a partner economically and with securitywould help",
      "shortname": "Immigration"
    },
    {
      "question": "Should the United States continue with the free trade policies it pursued for the last several decades, or should it enact restrictions in an attempt to help domestic industries?",
      "answer": "I believe in equal and fair trade without a trade War because Wars or nasty and there's always casualties, Mr. president.",
      "shortname": "Free trade"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you support the Iran nuclear deal?",
      "answer": "I support trans nuclear deal but there is room for improvement we need more people on the ground for verification",
      "shortname": "Iran"
    },
    {
      "question": "How should the United States address the rise of North Koreaâ€™s nuclear program?",
      "answer": "The key to North Korea is China . We should not isolate our friends and allies like this Administration is doing. also making it difficult for other countries to do business with North Korea. Having negotiations with North Korea and South Korea.",
      "shortname": "North Korea"
    }
  ],
  "race": "us-house",
  "residence": "Aberdeen",
  "survey-response": "LATE SUB",
  "title": "Anthony Sr. Carter"
}
